Guide to the University Governance Records RG 3
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series 8. University Senate, 42820
  - Requests for Approval
    - Requests for Administrative approval with no Resolution numbers, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      That the University Senate accepts the recommendations contained in Section II of the 1000-2000 Promotion and Tenure Committee Annual Report and that the appropriate Sections of the Faculty Handbook shall be modified accordingly.
    - Requests for administrative approval, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      Accessioned from Senate President Vijay Nair.
      R-00-10-04
      R-00-10-05
      R-00-11-03
      R-00-11-05
      R-00-09-06
      R-00-10-08
    - Requests for administrative approval, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 18-20)
      R-01-03-02
      R-01-03-08
      R-01-04-02
      R-01-04-04
      R-01-02-03
      R-01-02-04
      R-01-05-03
    - Requests for administrative approval, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      R-03-05-02
      R-03-04-02
    - Request for Discussion: Promotion and Tenure, 2004; 58655 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Requests for administrative approval, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      Accessioned from Vijay Nair.
      R-04-04-01
      R-04-03-02
      R-04-11-04
      R-04-12-10
      R-04-12-11
    - Requests for administrative approval, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      R-05-02-07
      R-05-02-06
      R-05-02-04
      R-05-02-05
    - Requests for administrative approval, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 17.1)
      R-06-04-04
    - Requests for administrative approval, 2007; 58654 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Requests for administrative approval, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      R-09-18-01
    - Requests for administrative approval, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      R-10-11-01
      R-10-11-02
      R-10-12-02
    - Requests for administrative approval, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      R-12-03-01
      R-12-03-02
      R-12-03-03
      R-12-03-04
      R-12-05-01
      R-12-05-02
      R-12-05-03
      R-12-05-04
      R-12-10-01
      R-12-10-02
      R-12-11-02
    - Requests for administrative approval, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      R-11-03-01
      R-11-03-02
      R-11-05-01
      R-11-10-01
      R-11-10-02
      R-11-10-03
      R-11-11-01
      R-11-12-01
    - Requests for administrative approval, 2013 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      R-13-02-01
      R-13-02-02
      R-13-05-01
      R-13-05-02
    - Requests for administrative approval, 2014 (Box 13, Folder 29)
      R-14-09-01
      R-14-09-02
      R-14-02-01
      R-14-02-02
      R-14-02-03
      R-14-03-01
      R-14-03-02
      R-14-04-01
      R-14-05-01
    - Requests for administrative approval, 2017 (Box 13, Folder 42)
      R-17-11-01 R-17-11-02 R-17-11-03 R-17-11-04 R-17-11-05 R-17-11-06
    - Requests for administrative approval, 2018 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Resolutions
    - Senate Resolutions, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Accessioned from Senate President Vijay Nair
      R-00-05-03
      R-00-05-06
      R-00-05-08
      R-00-05-09
      R-00-05-10
      R-00-05-12
      R-00-05-13
      R-00-05-14
    - Senate Resolutions, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
      R-01-03-03
      R-01-03-04
      R-01-03-05
      R-01-03-06
      R-01-04-03
      R-01-09-05
      R-01-10-02
      R-01-12-02
      R-01-09-06
      R-01-11-02
      R-01-11-03
    - Senate Resolutions, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 11-12)
      R-02-03-03
      R-02-03-02
      R-02-03-04
      R-02-03-05
      R-02-03-06
      R-02-03-07
      R-02-04-02
      R-02-04-03
      R-02-04-04
      R-02-04-08
      R-02-10-05
      R-02-10-06
    - Senate Resolution R-03-04-03, 2003; 42857 (Box 10a, Folder 1)
      R-03-04-03
    - Senate Resolutions, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      Accessioned from Vijay Nair
      R-03-09-03
      R-03-12-03
      R-03-12-04
    - Senate Resolutions, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 14-15)
      R-04-04-02
      R-04-09-04
      R-04-10-01
      R-04-12-01
    - Senate Resolutions, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Senate President's Files
    - Edwin Rosenberg's Files, Senate Minutes, 1967-1979; 42855 (Box 10a, Folder 3-18)
    - Vijay Nair Files, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 33)
      Materials include: correspondence, committee roster, and CSU forum announcement.
    - Vijay Nair Files, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 34)
      Materials include: Notes, Senate sign-in and availability sheet, and correspondence.
    - Vijay Nair Files, Senate Elections, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Vijay Nair Files, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 36)
      Materials include: correspondence, meeting room reservation confirmations, proposed resolutions regarding pre-emptive military force against Iraq, and materials relating to student protests that occurred in 2000.
    - Vijay Nair Files, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 37)
      Materials include: announcements, correspondence, photocopy of Chronicle of Higher Education article, Conference schedule, debate procedures, and senate sign-up for electronic delivery of materials.
    - Vijay Nair Files, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 38)
      Materials include: agendas, correspondence, announcements, drafts, strategic plan, reports, attendance sheets, and meeting schedules.
    - Vijay Nair Files, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 39)
      Materials include: correspondence, drafts, announcements, reports, forms, and policies.
    - Vijay Nair Files, Internal Review Board, 2004-2005 (Box 13, Folder 40)
      Materials include: correspondence, minutes, Dept. of Health and Human Services code of federal regulations, bylaws, and annual report.
    - Vijay Nair Files, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 41)
      Materials include: correspondence.
    - Karen Koza Files, 2011; 58656 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      Correspondence re: In-state tuition for undocumented students
- Series 9: University Planning and Budget Committee, 52876
  - Planning Documents (Revised 11/17/95), 1995; 52877 (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
  - Program Assessment, Ancell School, Professional Studies, 2001-2004; 52878 (Box 12, Folder 4-7)
  - Preliminary Academic Planning Report, Arts and Sciences, Academic Years 2001-04, 2001-2004; 52879 (Box 12, Folder 8-12)
  - Library Strategic Plan Documents, 1995; 52880 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Personnel Organizational Strategic Plan, 1995; 52881 (Box 12, Folder 14)